[
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 7) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "36",
      "31",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 1) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 7) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "19",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 2) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "55",
    "options": [
      "55",
      "51",
      "50",
      "57"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 1) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "12",
      "13",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 5) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "60",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "56",
      "62",
      "60"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 7) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "45",
      "35",
      "36"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 6) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "65",
    "options": [
      "61",
      "62",
      "64",
      "65"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 3) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "9",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 4) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "19",
      "26",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 1) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "14",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 7) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "24",
      "28",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 7) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "85",
    "options": [
      "87",
      "88",
      "81",
      "85"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 8) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "80",
    "options": [
      "85",
      "84",
      "80",
      "83"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 9) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "70",
    "options": [
      "65",
      "75",
      "70",
      "71"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 5) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "33",
      "32",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 10) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "14",
      "10",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 9) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "90",
    "options": [
      "90",
      "88",
      "95",
      "91"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 5) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "60",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "55",
      "56",
      "59"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 3) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "52",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "54",
      "47",
      "50"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 1) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "20",
      "18",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 3) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "14",
      "18",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 8) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "10",
      "14",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 4) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "50",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "49",
      "45",
      "55"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 7) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 4) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "30",
      "26",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 10) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "18",
      "20",
      "22"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 7) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "48",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "52",
      "48",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 5) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "10",
      "12",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 1) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "20",
      "17",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 2) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "60",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "63",
      "56",
      "55"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 3) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "19",
      "21",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 9) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "10",
      "17",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 4) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "19",
      "24",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 2) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "35",
      "31",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 4) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "45",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "45",
      "48",
      "47"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 2) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "12",
      "13",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 4) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "44",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "44",
      "43",
      "47"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 9) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "30",
      "28",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 6) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "25",
      "16",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 4) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "24",
      "20",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 8) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 8) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "44",
      "40",
      "42"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 3) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "45",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "44",
      "45",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 9) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "75",
    "options": [
      "71",
      "73",
      "74",
      "75"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 10) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "42",
      "43",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 2) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "32",
      "29",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 6) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "42",
      "38",
      "40"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 1) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "10",
      "16",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 7) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "45",
      "40",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 3) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "26",
      "28",
      "33"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 8) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "72",
    "options": [
      "69",
      "70",
      "68",
      "72"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 6) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "18",
      "16",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 1) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "34",
      "35",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 4) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "22",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 4) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "32",
      "31",
      "37"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 2) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "20",
      "18",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 7) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "26",
      "27",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 2) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "18",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 5) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "45",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "45",
      "50",
      "48"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 5) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "42",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "40",
      "42",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 4) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "28",
      "31",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 5) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "52",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "56",
      "48",
      "54"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 1) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "16",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 6) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "11",
      "6",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 9) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "18",
      "12",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 3) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "25",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "26",
      "27",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 4) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "34",
      "27",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 3) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "7",
      "2",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 9) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "70",
    "options": [
      "67",
      "65",
      "70",
      "68"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 2) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "9",
      "4",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 3) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "44",
      "40",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (1 + 2) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "8",
      "10",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 5) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "13",
      "15",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 8) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "36",
      "35",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 6) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "15",
      "8",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 2) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "34",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 3) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "36",
      "29",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 2) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "21",
      "18",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 4) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "35",
      "30",
      "32"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 1) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "44",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "48",
      "49",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 10) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "51",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "53",
      "56",
      "54"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 6) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "32",
      "31",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 2) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "35",
      "32",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 2) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "25",
      "24",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 1) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "20",
      "21",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 1) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "18",
      "11",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 7) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "75",
    "options": [
      "72",
      "71",
      "80",
      "75"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 5) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "45",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "43",
      "45",
      "46"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 1) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "7",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 7) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "13",
      "15",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 5) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "32",
      "36",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (9 + 3) \u00d7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "23",
      "24",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 3) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "32",
      "30",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 9) \u00d7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "65",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "63",
      "60",
      "65"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 10) \u00d7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "36",
      "34",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (5 + 4) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "12",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 5) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "44",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "44",
      "42",
      "40"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 4) \u00d7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "35",
      "34",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 2) \u00d7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "2",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 6 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "19",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 10 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "15",
      "20",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 9 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 7 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "17",
      "15",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 4 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "19",
      "23",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 3 + 5 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "0",
      "5",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 9 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "17",
      "19",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 2 \u00f7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 8 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "24",
      "21",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 1 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "15",
      "18",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 2 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "16",
      "17",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 8 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "9",
      "8",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 18 + 9 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "18",
      "21",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 2 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "16",
      "17",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 3 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "15",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 6 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "8",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 12 + 5 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "13",
      "12",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 10 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "11",
      "8",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 1 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "13",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 7 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "0",
      "-2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 1 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "15",
      "16",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 10 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "18",
      "16",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 5 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "11",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 10 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 3 + 3 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "5",
      "3",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 5 \u00f7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "18",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 9 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "12",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 7 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "14",
      "15",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 9 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "6",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 4 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "21",
      "24",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 6 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "-1",
      "-2",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 3 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "9",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 1 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "17",
      "19",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 9 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 4 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "7",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 7 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "13",
      "11",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 8 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "19",
      "20",
      "22"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 10 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "12",
      "10",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 3 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "24",
      "23",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 9 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "8",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 6 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "4",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 1 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 1 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "5",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 2 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "14",
      "13",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 5 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 5 \u00f7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "18",
      "20",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 6 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "8",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 2 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "15",
      "17",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 5 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "5",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 10 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "13",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 7 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "15",
      "14",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 8 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "18",
      "17",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 8 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 7 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "18",
      "17",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 3 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "16",
      "14",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 8 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "16",
      "15",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 7 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "10",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 3 + 3 \u00f7 10?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "3",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 7 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "17",
      "21",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 5 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "6",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 3 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "13",
      "18",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 6 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "17",
      "20",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 10 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "8",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 5 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "24",
      "21",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 8 + 8 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "7",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 3 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "13",
      "14",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 10 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "2",
      "0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 1 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 7 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 8 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "25",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "24",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 9 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "24",
      "20",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 1 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "11",
      "8",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 4 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "3",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 10 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "19",
      "14",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 6 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 3 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "21",
      "19",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 9 \u00f7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "14",
      "15",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 2 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "19",
      "21",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 7 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "19",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 6 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "10",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 10 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 5 \u00f7 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "4",
      "2",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 6 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "7",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 10 + 1 \u00f7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "10",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 3 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "15",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 5 + 8 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "3",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 3 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "4",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 1 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "20",
      "16",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 3 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "20",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 8 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "22",
      "20",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 1 \u00f7 1?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "19",
      "18",
      "17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 18 + 4 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "20",
      "19",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 4 \u00f7 4?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 6 \u00f7 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "3",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 19 + 9 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "21",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 17 + 7 \u00f7 8?",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "17",
      "16",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 15 + 9 \u00f7 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "15",
      "14",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 2 + 8 \u00f7 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "9",
      "6",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 11 + 5 \u00f7 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "12",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result <br> of 6 + 9 \u00f7 5?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 9 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "23",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "24",
      "23",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 4 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "14",
      "9",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 3 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "13",
      "12",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 1 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "32",
      "25",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 3 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "8",
      "0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 9 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "11",
      "14",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 4 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "37",
      "34",
      "33"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 8 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "18",
      "16",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 8 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "19",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 0 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 8 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "21",
      "14",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 4 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "28",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "28",
      "24",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 3 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "14",
      "15",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 4 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "13",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 4 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "6",
      "15",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 4 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "35",
      "40",
      "44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 1 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "9",
      "-1",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 1 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "11",
      "14",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 5 when x = 3",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "20",
      "21",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 3 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "31",
      "33",
      "28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 2 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "21",
      "27",
      "22"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 9 when x = 3",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "20",
      "18",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 10 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "9",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 7 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "43",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "42",
      "41",
      "43"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 1 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "17",
      "20",
      "22"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 4 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "5",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 5 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "11",
      "13",
      "4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 10 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "11",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 1 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "8",
      "7",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 6 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "26",
      "31",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 10 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "14",
      "15",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 7 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "57",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "55",
      "57",
      "54"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 2 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "11",
      "12",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 2 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "6",
      "5",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 8 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "32",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "37",
      "35",
      "36"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 4 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "11",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 4 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "22",
      "18",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 9 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "21",
      "14",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 8 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "22",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "21",
      "22",
      "26"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 5 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "23",
      "18",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 8 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "22",
      "18",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 9 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "27",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "28",
      "27",
      "30"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 9 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "32",
      "25",
      "35"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 7 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "42",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "45",
      "46",
      "37"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 9 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "29",
      "32",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 8 when x = 3",
    "correctAnswer": "17",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "17",
      "22",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 1 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "25",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "29",
      "28",
      "25"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 4 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "21",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 3 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "11",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 1 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "25",
      "18",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 2 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "29",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "29",
      "25",
      "27"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 8 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "53",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "52",
      "53",
      "55"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 8 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "53",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "58",
      "53",
      "57"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 6 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "26",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "31",
      "26",
      "29"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 9 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "22",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 0 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "45",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "44",
      "42",
      "48"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 10 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "30",
      "33",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 0 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "4",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 0 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "4",
      "6",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 8 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "33",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "31",
      "37",
      "33"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 6 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "17",
      "22",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 8 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "34",
      "36",
      "33"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 5 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "25",
      "24",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 1 when x = 3",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "-1",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 1 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "15",
      "17",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 1 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "21",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "23",
      "17",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 0 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "21",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 6 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "36",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "34",
      "37",
      "41"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 4 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "24",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "25",
      "21",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 5 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "23",
      "19",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 8 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "35",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "35",
      "32",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 3 when x = 3",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "12",
      "19",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 1 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "25",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "30",
      "22",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 5 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "17",
      "18",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 1 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "11",
      "6",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 10 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "14",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "11",
      "15",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 2 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "18",
      "22",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 0 when x = 9",
    "correctAnswer": "27",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "23",
      "27",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 10 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "34",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "36",
      "34",
      "31"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 1 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "8",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 10 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "15",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 2 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "13",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 8 when x = 3",
    "correctAnswer": "20",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "21",
      "16",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 1 when x = 6",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "17",
      "20",
      "19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 1 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "17",
      "18",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 7 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "15",
      "11",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 6 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "16",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "11",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 2x + 7 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "27",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "27",
      "32",
      "24"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 5 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "41",
      "42",
      "38"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 4 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "6",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "2",
      "10",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 10 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "30",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "35",
      "30",
      "26"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 3 when x = 2",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "9",
      "8",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 10 when x = 5",
    "correctAnswer": "15",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "13",
      "15",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 4x + 10 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "42",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "42",
      "39",
      "47"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 6 when x = 7",
    "correctAnswer": "13",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "13",
      "11",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 7 when x = 4",
    "correctAnswer": "11",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "7",
      "11",
      "6"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 1x + 4 when x = 1",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "0",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 3x + 4 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "34",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "29",
      "30",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 3 when x = 10",
    "correctAnswer": "53",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "58",
      "48",
      "53"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Evaluate the expression <br> of 5x + 0 when x = 8",
    "correctAnswer": "40",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "40",
      "42",
      "43"
    ]
  }
]